[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
What are you doing here?
Toto came by.
I can't believe you.
You're willing to throw
your own brother in jail.
- You don't know anything--
- All I know is
you're filthy rich,
but you're too stingy
to help your own brother!
[SCOFFS]
Me, stingy?
Ever since we were younger,
he's been addicted to gambling.
He even gambled away
his tuition money.
When he got arrested,
I bailed him out right away.
I got him a job with Don Nato,
but what happened?
He stole just
so he could gamble.
And what did I do?
Nothing...
Because all I did
was defend my brother.
I even got him a job
at Pindang Tocino,
but he just wouldn't stop.
Every chance he got,
he'd take more and more.
His gambling addiction
just kept getting worse.
So, June,
as much as it hurts me,
I have to let him face
the consequences.
Because I'm not the only one
affected by this.
Our employees will suffer too
if we go under because of him.
So tell me, June...
am I really that terrible
of a brother?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
There you go!
That's more like it.
You should apologize
to me, June.
[DOOR OPENS]
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
W-What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
I heard you two arguing.
W-We're okay. Good night.
W-Wait, Ping!
[JUNE] We're not having
a lovers' quarrel anymore.
That was our first real fight.
Ugh!
But Ima said,
married couples shouldn't stay
mad at each other for too long.
Are we a married couple?!
What happened to us?
We used to be very close.
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JUNE] Fine. I'll be the first
to apologize
since I started it anyway.
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
You cheaters!
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]